Good morning, and welcome to the next installment of the "Good Morning" series.
We are here to talk about the coupling of Equal Love's 14th single.
This is the 14th single, and it's Equal Love's self-introduction song.
Eee! Finally!
We made a self-introduction song for Equal Love.
Wow! Yay!
Let's listen to the demo first.
Yes, it has no lyrics.
There are no lyrics.
Why? Why now?
I'm just saying,
You know what I mean,
There are no lyrics.
I'm just making it up as I go along.
I'm going to ask the members to write lyrics for the first time for the first half of the song.
For the first time, we are asking the members to write the lyrics.
Five in the first and five in the second.
We are going to have a party where we are going to introduce the octopus.
Who will introduce who's octopus?
We're going to draw lots now.
A raffle?
Is that true?
First, let's see who's going to be which clocks.
What?
The butt of the draw?
Yes, sir.
Here we go.
Number two, D.
Oh, my God.
Number 2 "D"?
Otoshima-san, you introduce someone's octopus in the second D.
That's the part you sing.
Fast forward.
Now that we've decided on the order in which we'll sing the first and second parts...
After that, we'll have to decide who to introduce by scratching.
I can't help it with the costumes.
I'll decide.
I've made a scratch-off lottery.
We'll use that to decide who's going to be the last member.
I didn't have the placement in the demo.
There was a flow.
And then I think there was a break two bars in.
And at that break, the person who was introduced
the person who was introduced at the break would say his or her signature line.
Well, what's the clincher?
I came up with my own cliché.
Can I write it every time?
Live or otherwise?
Well, if it's a live show...
"I like your mouth.
You don't like it when I say it.
That would be nice.
It's a dream, isn't it?
Okay, well, I'll hand them out.
You're doing it?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Are you?
I think you're doing it.
Oh, my God.
That was so neat.It was so neat.
Here.
Okay, let's start with number 1A, Chiara.
Okay, here we go.
Who's up? Here we go.
Ah!
Look at you!
Oh!
That's great!
Let's do this.
In the best picture.
Hiara-chan is
Sasaki's
After introducing his face and saying "flow
Mr. Sasaki says the following lines
He's saying it.
I don't see it at all.
That's good.
Let's do that.
Okay, then. BORO HOUSE
This is Chanby.
I'm Chanby.
Yes, you must be Mr. New Year's Eve. Let me introduce Mr. BORO HOUSE to you, Mr. New Year's Eve.
Okay, then.
I know this already.
Tatachan.
In a moment.
Tatachan, right?
Yes, I'll introduce Mr. Borough House to you, Mr. New Year's Eve.
Then let's do it, even the two of you.
Then!
Rio!
Yes, we've got you two.
Let's go, leader.
Yes!
Sho, Shoko!
Shoko!
Yes, the leader
Mr. Takeuchi has been defeated.
Yes, the best. It's over.
Yes, it's fun.
Let's go to the second member.
Okay, let's go to number 2, A, Sasaki.
Okay, here we go.
Oh, you got it right.
Hitomi.
Oh...
Hitomi
That's so cute!
Mr. Sasaki will choose Mr. Takamatsu
Here we go.
Oh, it's Kihara!
It's Kihara!
Spoiler alert!
Let's do it!
Yay!
Let's go, Mr. Sasaki!
Okay, okay.
Yes, in the race, Wan Li.
Yes, front.Yes, front
Together at the same time
Top together
Oh, my gosh!
Oh!
Mr. New Year's Eve...
Mr. Morohaya, isn't it?
Yes, Mr. Sasaki is
Mr. Honda
You have our names in the lyrics.
Goal lamp
Well, that's all for today.
Thank you for your hard work
I never thought I'd be singing the lyrics.
Fans are now allowed to speak up at live concerts and so on.
I'm sure it's going to be a lot of fun. I'm looking forward to it.
I heard that it's the same as last time.
I've been introducing the lyrics to everyone at the shows.
It's going to be in the lyrics.
It's a big deal. It's a big deal.
And the lyric cards.
Yeah.
It's a big responsibility.
But I've been doing a lot of gigs.
Anna often introduced me to the audience, so...
for sure.
I think I could think of a way to thank you there.
There are so many words, it's hard to summarize them.
Same?
Certainly.
Oh no!
It's like, "I want to put this together, but this doesn't fit.
I don't even think about what's good.
I'm really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really, really.
It's too scary.
I don't know.
I'm scared.
I'm looking forward to it because it's my first time with Miryan. Thinking about it.
I'm just thinking about it.
It's great!
I'm looking forward to hearing what you have to say and what words you would like me to include in the song,
I hope I can think of a song with them in it.
I'll do my best! Enjoy!
Enjoy!
Good morning, everyone!
Today, we will introduce ourselves. Have you thought about it by pairing up?
Yes!
Well, today I would like to present them to you!
Let's start with number 1...number 1?
Let's start with number one.
I'd like to start with Chiara!
Then, please do!
Cute, charming beans, two-sided tints, all perfect.
Oh!
I'm a little out of vocabulary and couldn't fit it all in, so I had to guess four kanji characters.
Oh, I see!
Like a four-character idiom.
Chiara is using a four-character idiom. That's amazing.Chiara is using four-letter words. That's great.
It's not a four-letter word.
It's a four-character idiom!
What kind of idioms?
It's too fragile.
The endings are a little bit infelicitous. Like...
Mermaid and perfect.
I'm so happy!
Thank you!
Sana thought of Risa's.
I flew in from the land of Princesses, the official girlfriend of Equal Love and,
I'm so glad you like it!
I added a heart.
I added a heart, too.
Well, Risa did, too.
Both of them.
Then, Hitomi.
I drew a picture of a wrap.
Oh, sorry. I messed up the letters.
Yes, yes, Tonkatsu is,
Roo overflows, Mai, A, Hana, Yaka, Shoutan, Kimi, Ogoshoutan.
Wow, it's perfect.
Perfect! Thank you very much.
Next, Minyan.
I have written the lyrics for Yuri.
Hardworking genius performance.
A pampered gap.
A cheater who steps around for everyone.
It's good.
Please.
First meeting?
Well, then, at the end of the most, I wrote Shoko.
Challenge anything, active girl, BPM up when you see the effort!
I like it.
I wanted to include the word BPM, so I did.
Thank you very much.
Okay, then, let's move on to number 2.
The first one, Maika, please.
When we love each other, our feelings will increase. Your smile will be warm. You are the sun.
You are the sun.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I wanted to put the word "sun," so I did.
It's good.
It's nice to have love in there too.
At first Maika-chan called me AYE for EYE.
I said, "What is that?
It was close.
It was EYE.
Then, let's continue.
I was still a little lost, and He wrote two.
Great.
One, sweet angel. Devil's temptation. Love to put in a candy voice.
That's great.
It's like a go-yu-chan.
Powerful.
Sweetly melting enchanting angel. Devil's spice plus extra.
Cute.
It's cute, isn't it?
I wanted to include angels and demons.I wanted to include angels and demons.
It bothers me.
I'm glad. Thank you so much for including so many.
I'm amazed. Your vocabulary is amazing.
Vocabulary?
I think you're wrong.
It's really elaborate.
I can't wait to see which one it's going to be.
It's going to be very different.
Isn't that everyone?
Okay, let's continue.
I'm sorry, I'm full of English.
Here we go.
Here we are, our leader. Lil' Lil' Lil' is here for the dance.
Wow, that's great.
That's great. That's so cool.
Too cool.
I put a lot of hip-hop slang into it, so it would be a sick dance if I translated it directly.
I don't know how it will turn out yet, but it will be like this.
Thank you very much. You're all set.
Next is Risa.
We are in love with each other.
That's right.
With February's Nikola Club Diva Green.
My stomach is rumbling. Sorry.
If I don't tell you, you'll know.
I'll change my mind.
I'm in charge of Green, the diva of the Nicola Club. Everyone is taken in by her enchanting voice. I will sing for you.
I'm glad. Thank you.
Nice. I put it in because Barrier has a lovely voice.
And the last one soon.
It's beautiful.
Okay, last one.
Please introduce me.
I'm Miriya.
Makeup, fashion, and stylish Mya Mya. I'm Ms. Otani, a girl's dream.
I like her. Ms. Otani.
I haven't thought of any other words I want to include yet, but I'm not sure how it will turn out,
I'm not sure how it will turn out, but I'd like to include Ms. Otani.
I don't know how it will turn out, but I would like to include it.
I'm sure you had a lot of trouble. It took us all about a day to think about it,
There is a possibility that we may have to make some changes from here, but for now, let's just do our best and try recording in pre-production after today.
Please look forward to seeing how the song will turn out.
Good morning.
I'll do my best!
I'm the only one who looks like a cheerleader today.
Let me put on my ribbon and be merry!
Ta-da!
Let me greet you!
Good morning!
Thank you very much for the fall-up disc and everyone.
It's a pleasure to play for you.
Thank you very much.
I just wanted to do a bit of a barter-in.
I hope I can sing the song with the same sound as before.
May I?
Enjoy the next episode!
N.O.V.E.
Invitationinvitation
Mai-chan
Stay close to me all the time
Nico's Official
Enkachan
Because I flew in from the land of needs
N.O.V.E
Enjoy!
Lisa
Let me come to you
Country Love
N.O.V.E.
Don't always take my picture
N.O.V.E. is out in the open.
Oh, I don't have a picture.
I wondered why everyone was taking pictures of
I was wondering what they're all taking pictures with.
I'm taking pictures with that thing on the panel.
The dance is over!
It's so hard!
The dance is over! We did it!
It was hot,
It was a lot of fun.
There are so many parts of this song that I want the fans to do.
First of all, I'd like to introduce my Lisa for the part where she's allowed to speak out loud.
The official equalizer!
I said, "She! and they'd shout out "She!
I said, "She's the official Equal Love! When I say, "She! please shout "she!
And then there's that koromochiko
Ta-ta, ta-ta, ta-ta, ta-ta
I want you to do that too.
And L.O.V.E.
And I want you to do the members' names, too.
I'm busy!
I hope you all have a lot of fun!
All the more!
I danced a lot!
I was challenging myself not to take off any of my clothes.
I did it alone, one at a time.
No particular reason.
I wanted to know my limits.
I didn't take it off at first.
I came this far and I didn't want to take it off.
I was stubborn.
This is Yamamoto from Recall Love TV.
Today, Shoko Takewaki, a member of the Recall Club, is running here.
So we're here to take a break.
Shoko Takewaki running
So cute!
Yay!
It's so nice!
I ran again today
I've been running for music videos recently.
I usually run by myself, but this time there was a cheering crowd and a finish line tape, so it was a really fun shoot.
I'm looking forward to the part where the other members introduce themselves.
It's pretty chaotic.
He came to pick me up.
That's so nice.
That's too good.
Too much!spear-shaped Japanese cedar
Imitating Ha-chan
Ha-chan is too good.
I gave it to her.
No! Don't do that eyebrow thing!
Such eyebrows...
She's a genius!
Try it, then!
Okay!
Just take it!
Seriously?
Come on, I don't want to give it to this guy!
I'm serious!
If you don't accept it easily...
I can't do silver!
I want it!
How was it?
It was fun. Everyone was in a groove and everyone was so excited.
It was great!
Thanks everyone! Thank you!
I am now a Sure King!
From father to mother
Sake-boiling-san, O-hoshi-shin-san, Sanza-san!
But you were the mastermind in the cartoon.
Yes! The mastermind!
Your father!
Your mom's a performance genius.
She's a spoiled brat!
Everyone's going to pay her a visit... soon enough.
Huh! Aah! Soooo! Aah! No! Hu! Sh! color! I love you!
Do you like me, Iiichan?
Welcome!
Ready!
Oh, my God!
Yes!
Ready!
Hey, Ka-To!
Yes!
Seee-hee!
Oh, heel!
One more!
Oh!
Here you go!
Yes, yes... No, it's okay...
It'll be fine.
It was a lot of fun... at first I didn't know what to do.
But everyone was so excited and we had a scene with 2 shots with everyone...
I'm looking forward to seeing the finished product.
I can't wait to see the finished product!
huh?
none melanin g
I'm going to switch to a different one for various reasons.
the manager
g
10 changes.
Ready?
Yes, sir.
I'm not looking at the process.I've never seen the process before.
I've never seen the process of tubing teeth before.
It was so much fun.
You can see how long it took to make.
Oh yeah!
Whose hand is this?
Not this one?
Hand in hand.
It's a line at first.
Oh!
I! I!
I! Two!
I! Three!
I! Four!
Stay by my side all the way
Through the Gorakumon
Wow!
They looked like they were having a lot of fun.
The people in the back
I enjoyed it.
But I have one concern.
When you showed me the first one.
I thought, "Wow, my chin is really up.
I thought I was going to lower my chin.
but my chin was definitely up.
I'm a little bit worried about it.
But you said it was OK, so I guess it's OK.
Yes, sir.
We built this venue.
Galagon.
Come on, let's try it and see what happens.
I haven't felt this way in a long time
We had fun then, too.
Yes, let's go.
What? It's amazing.
Um, one-too-one-two.
To the 4th single, Wangchoo Wangchoo Valley.
Ride in this cart.
I used this to talk while I was doing it.
I did it!
Thank you, Hana-chan!
I'm so happy!
It's been a while since I rode on this cart.
I didn't think I'd get to shoot a music video.
I'm so happy.
Are you hearing this?
That's great.
I'm so nervous.
Thank you for watching.
Can it be you and me again tonight?
I kind of winked at you, it was fun.
I tried to say a slightly different line from "Ricolabuno".
Sho-kun came up with the lyrics this time,
I think he changed the lyrics a few times.
He seemed to have thought of a lot of lyrics that he changed several times.
Notice how everyone falls over!
I'm here to serve you, Ero-kun!
Come to pick me up!
Ai kaka kaka!Aikaka!
Tea is the best thing ever!
Cut!
Yes, sir.
You're all so good!
Yes, please.
After the scene we just shot.
While the members are helping me with various things...
We didn't rehearse any fruit or anything like that.
So I wondered what was going to happen all of a sudden.
But it was so fresh and new
I felt like I was having a good time.
Did you feel like you were in the right mood?
Yes! I'm looking forward to the completion of the project.
How was it?
Love is a feeling that rises
Smile, I'll always sing from where
You are the idol
Enconnery
Eyes with power
I'll light up everyone
Perfect!
It's a little difficult.
With the height,
Yes, I just finished my scene,
It was shot in such a big place in total darkness,
I was so happy to have everyone remember me, and at the end, I was able to light up the whole scene,
I was so happy.
Risa was dancing while holding the three of us like this,
I feel grateful to her.
I also had a lot of fun taking pictures of everyone,
I had a lot of fun taking pictures of everyone, but I also really like my part,
Please check out my part in detail.
It's so good!
This place is so nice.
I had a great time.
This one that surrounds me and my place is so funny,
And it's cool, and I think it's the most surreal scene,
I think it's the most surreal scene, so please watch it a lot.
Everyone is doing their own very interesting things,
Please pay attention to it.
Dancing, dancing, dancing, dancing, dancing, dancing, dancing, dancing, dancing, dancing, dancing, dancing, dancing, dancing, dancing, dancing!
S! O! V! E!
Ana Yamamoto!
Heart to your heart!
Yes, it's over.
I made her do it. I laughed.
I laughed.
Bye bye.
Okay, good.
Nine, one, two, three, four, five,
Yeah!
Bye-bye.
Ready, close.
One, two, three, four, five.
Yay.
This way.
Ready, pause.Ready, pause.
One, two, three, four, five.
Yay.
Over there.
One, two, three, four, five, whoa!
Rampage, rampage, rampage, rampage.
Let's go!
Ready, set, go!
One, two, three, four, five, yay, yay, yay, yay.
Stand up pretty. Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Ready, go! Riot, riot, riot, riot, riot!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Ew.
arm cracked
STOP!
Whiff!
one
Two.
three
fukuguei
Kuh.
Go back.
Yes, yes, yes
registered
Good.
One, two, three, four, five.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
That's good. That's good. That's good.
Thank you.
Yo.
Laughter
Laughter.
(Laughs)
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you so much for another really fun day of shooting!
I'm really looking forward to the shoot!
Thank you for all your hard work
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for your hard work.
We're done... all the shooting is done.
It took 1 hour and 2 hours to finish.
That's what I'm talking about, Makinori Collaboration!
Are you tired, Maika?
I'm afraid you'll get reflections in the mirror.
Okay.
The shooting is over!
The staff worked so hard from morning till night, and the members were all smiling and cheerful from the beginning to the end.
The members were all smiling and in good spirits from the beginning to the end of the shoot.
I'm relieved.
It was a lot of fun.
Since we were the heroines, we were the center of the group.
I'm the center of the group, but I've never been in a role like this before.
But this song is the best one so far in which everyone plays the leading role and everyone is a heroine.
It's a song where everyone is a heroine.
We are the main characters, but I think the fans are the main characters too.
but I think the fans are the main characters too.
So, I hope we can work together at live concerts and so on.
LOVE or Ojime
Calling out the names of all the membersCall out the names of all the members
I hope that we can make this music together.
It was a fun shoot!
Thank you very much for your hard work
Subtitle by Miku Hatsune
Thank you for watching!
Together!
Everyone!
Oshaaa!
Together!
Whoo-hoo!
Yeah!
Good job!
Yes, thank you!
Let's go!
Whoooo!
Yes!
Ok!